Guide to the Ira Nowinski collection, ca. 1965-2000
Department of Special Collections
- Holocaust Collection, Series 1
  - 50th Anniversary of Warsaw Ghetto Uprising, Sub-series 1.2
    - Prints
      - People: Warsaw, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 7, Folder 16)
        Images from contact sheet Poland - 47
      - People: Warsaw, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 7, Folder 17)
        Images from contact sheet Poland - 48
      - People: Warsaw, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 7, Folder 18)
        Images from contact sheet Poland - 49
      - People: Warsaw, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 7, Folder 19)
        Images from contact sheet Poland - 50
      - People: Warsaw, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 7, Folder 20)
        Images from contact sheet Poland - 53
      - People: Warsaw, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 7, Folder 21)
        Images from contact sheet Poland - 72
      - People: Warsaw, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 7, Folder 22)
        Images from contact sheet Poland - 74
      - People: Warsaw, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 7, Folder 23)
        Images from contact sheet Poland - 77
      - People: Warsaw, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 7, Folder 24)
        Images from contact sheet Poland - 79
      - People: Warsaw, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 7, Folder 25)
        Images from contact sheet Poland - 81
      - People: Warsaw, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 7, Folder 26)
        Images from contact sheet Poland - 84
      - People: Warsaw, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 7, Folder 27)
        Images from contact sheet Poland - 89
      - People: Warsaw, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Prints, Large
      - Poland: 50th Anniversary of the Warsaw Ghetto Uprising, photographs: b&w; 34 x 28 cm. (Box 25)
    - Prints, Oversize
      - Poland: 50th Anniversary of the Warsaw Ghetto Uprising: Birkenau, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Poland: 50th Anniversary of the Warsaw Ghetto Uprising: Treblinka, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Poland: 50th Anniversary of the Warsaw Ghetto Uprising: Warsaw, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Segal Holocaust Memorial, Sub-series 1.3
    This sub-series contains contact sheets and photographic prints in several sizes produced by Ira Nowinski in his photographic study of George Segal's sculpture honoring the victims of the Holocaust, which was installed in San Francisco in 1984.
    - Contact sheets
      - George Segal Holocaust Memoral: contact sheets 1 - 13 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        Segal Studio, 1983, and construction of memorial in San Francisco, 1984
      - George Segal Holocaust Memoral: contact sheets 14 - 21 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        Views of the Holocaust Memorial, San Francisco, 1984; night views of the Holocaust Memorial, San Francisco, 1984; images of defacement of memorial; images of dedication ceremony
      - George Segal Holocaust Memoral: contact sheets 22 - 34 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        Holocaust Memorial Day, San Francisco, 1985; Auschwitz Liberation Day, 1995; and 50th Anniversary of Liberation from Auschwitz
    - Prints
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 1)
        Images from contact sheet Segal - 1
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 2)
        Images from contact sheet Segal - 2
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 3)
        Images from contact sheet Segal - 3
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 4)
        Images from contact sheet Segal - 4
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 5)
        Images from contact sheet Segal - 5
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 6)
        Images from contact sheets Segal - 6 - 7
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 7)
        Images from contact sheets Segal - 8 - 11
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 8)
        Images from contact sheets Segal - 13 - 14
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 9)
        Images from contact sheets Segal - 15 - 20
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 10)
        Images from contact sheets Segal - 33 - 34
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 11)
        Images from contact sheets Segal - 21 - 31
    - Prints, Large
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, photographs: b&w; 34 x 28 cm. (Box 23)
    - Prints, Oversize
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, no. 1, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 24, Folder 3)
        Images from contact sheets Segal - 1 to Segal - 2
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, no. 2, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 24, Folder 4)
        Images from contact sheets Segal - 3 to Segal - 10
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, no. 3, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 24, Folder 5)
        Images from contact sheets Segal - 11 to Segal - 16
      - Segal Holocaust Memorial, no. 4, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 24, Folder 6)
        Images from contact sheets Segal - 17 to Segal - 27 + unidentified
  - U.S. Holocaust Museum opening, Sub-series 1.4
    This sub-series contains contact sheets and photographic prints in several sizes produced by Ira Nowinski in his photographic study of the opening of the United States Holocaust Museum.
    - Contact sheets
      - U.S. Holocaust Museum: contact sheets (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Prints
      - United States Holocaust Memorial opening, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 12)
        Images from contact sheets USHM - 1 - 10
      - United States Holocaust Memorial opening, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
        Images from unidentified USHM -contact sheet
- Judaica Photographs, Series 2
  This series contains contact sheets and photographic prints in several sizes produced by Ira Nowinski in his photographic study of Jewish life in the United States, Israel, and Egypt. In particular, it contains images of Karaite Jews in Foster City, Israel and Egypt, as well as images of Soviet Jews who had immigrated to San Francisco.
  - Karaite Jews, Sub-series 2.1
    This sub-series contains contact sheets and photographic prints in several sizes produced by Ira Nowinski in his photographic study of the lives of Karaite Jews in the United States, Israel, and Egypt. In particular, it contains images of daily life in Foster City, various sites in Israel and in Cairo, Egypt.
    - Contact sheets
      - Karaite Jews, California: contact sheets (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Karaite Jews: contact sheets 1 - 13 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        Egypt
      - Karaite Jews: contact sheets 14 - 30 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        Jerusalem; Ashdad; Ramlah
      - Karaite Jews: contact sheets 31 - 42 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        Jerusalem
      - Karaite Jews: contact sheets 43 - 51 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        Tel Aviv
      - Karaite Jews, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Prints
      - Karaite Jews - California, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite/California - 1
      - Karaite Jews - California, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
        Images from contact sheets Karaite/California - 2 to 4
      - Karaite Jews - California, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 16)
        Images from contact sheets Karaite/California - 5 to 6
      - Karaite Jews - California, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 1)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite/California - 8
      - Karaite Jews - California, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 2)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite/California - 10
      - Karaite Jews - California, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 3)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite/California - 11
      - Karaite Jews - California, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 4)
        Images from contact sheets Karaite/California - 12 - 16
      - Karaite Jews - Egypt, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 5)
        Images from contact sheets Karaite- 1 - 2
      - Karaite Jews - Egypt, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 6)
        Images from contact sheets Karaite- 3 - 4
      - Karaite Jews - Egypt, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 7)
        Images from contact sheets Karaite- 5 - 8
      - Karaite Jews - Egypt, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 8)
        Images from contact sheets Karaite- 9 - 10
      - Karaite Jews - Egypt, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 9)
        Images from contact sheets Karaite- 11 - 12
      - Karaite Jews - Israel, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 10)
        Images from contact sheets Karaite- 14 - 22
      - Karaite Jews - Israel, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 11)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite- 25
      - Karaite Jews - Israel, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 12)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite- 26
      - Karaite Jews - Israel, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 13)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite- 27
      - Karaite Jews - Israel, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 14)
        Images from contact sheets Karaite- 28 - 30
      - Karaite Jews - Israel, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 15)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite - 31
      - Karaite Jews - Israel, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 16)
        Images from contact sheets Karaite - 33 - 36
      - Karaite Jews - Israel, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 17)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite - 37
      - Karaite Jews - Israel, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 18)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite - 38
      - Karaite Jews - Israel, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 19)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite - 40
      - Karaite Jews - Israel, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 20)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite - 41
      - Karaite Jews - Israel, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 21)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite - 43
      - Karaite Jews - Israel, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 22)
        Images from contact sheet Karaite - 51
      - Karaite Jews - Karaite 1989, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Prints, Large
      - Karaite Jews, photographs: b&w; 34 x 28 cm. (Box 27)
    - Prints, Oversize
      - Karaite Jews: California, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Karaite Jews: Egypt, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Karaite Jews: Israel, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Karaite Jews, 1989, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Project files
      - Karaite Jews: [correspondence, clippings, & notes] (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jews in San Francisco, Sub-series 2.2
    This sub-series contains contact sheets and photographic prints in several sizes produced by Ira Nowinski in his photographic study of Soviet Jews who had immigrated to the San Francisco Bay Area.
    - Business cards
      - Soviet Jews: business cards, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Contact sheets
      - Soviet Jews in San Francisco: contact sheets 1 - 15 (Box 3, Folder 1)
        Music practice; Violin performance; Butchers; Grocers; Hair salons; Dancing
      - Soviet Jews in San Francisco: contact sheets 16 - 30 (Box 3, Folder 2)
        Menorah Park Senior Housing; Weddings; Painters; Domestic life
      - Soviet Jews in San Francisco: contact sheets 31 - 45 (Box 3, Folder 3)
        Protests; Domestic life; Artists
      - Soviet Jews in San Francisco: contact sheets 46 - 60 (Box 3, Folder 4)
        Jewish Community Center, San Francisco (Calif.); Passover; War heroes -- Soviet
      - Soviet Jews in San Francisco: contact sheets 61 - 75 (Box 3, Folder 5)
        War heroes -- Soviet; Musical performances; Protests; Laudries; Cobblers; Dentists
      - Soviet Jews in San Francisco: contact sheets 76 - 90 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        Includes some images of Karaite Jews (see sheet 79)
        Jewish Vocational Services Emigre Project, San Francisco (Calif.); Family life; Bar mitzvah
      - Soviet Jews in San Francisco: contact sheets 91 - 105 (Box 3, Folder 7)
        Lemkin, Misha; Weddings; Receptions; Cemeteries
      - Soviet Jews in San Francisco: contact sheets 106 - 120 (Box 3, Folder 8)
        Lemkin, Misha; Domestic life; Butchers; Markets; Family photographs
      - Soviet Jews in San Francisco: contact sheets 121 - 135 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        Lemkin, Misha; Bar mitzvahs; Protests; Wedding
      - Soviet Jews in San Francisco: contact sheets 136 - 150 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        Eilinkring Family; Cobblers; Grocers; Rabbis; Protests
      - Soviet Jews in San Francisco: contact sheets 151 - 165 (Box 3, Folder 11)
        Protests; Passover
      - Soviet Jews in San Francisco: contact sheets 166 - 180 (Box 3, Folder 12)
        Schools; Senior centers; Hanukkah
    - Prints
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 2)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -1 to 10
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 3)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -11 to 20
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 4)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -21 to 30
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 5)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -31 to 40
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 6)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -41 to 50
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 7)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -51 to 60
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 8)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -61 to 70
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 9)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -71 to 80
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 10)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -81 to 90
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 11)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -91 to 100
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 12)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -101 to 110
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 13)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -111 to 120
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 14)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -121 to 130
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 15)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -131 to 135
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 16)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -136 to 140
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 17)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -141 to 150
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 18)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -151 to 160
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 19)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -161 to 170
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 20)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews -171 to 180
      - Soviet Jews, Photographic prints: b&w; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Prints, Large
      - Soviet Jews, photographs: b&w; 34 x 28 cm. (Box 29)
    - Prints, Oversize
      - Soviet Jews, no. 1, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 30, Folder 1)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews - 1, 3, & 9
      - Soviet Jews, no. 2, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 30, Folder 2)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews - 16, 18, 21, & 25
      - Soviet Jews, no. 3, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 30, Folder 3)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews - 46, 53, 54, 59, & 60
      - Soviet Jews, no. 4, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 30, Folder 4)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews - 66, 76, & 77
      - Soviet Jews, no. 5, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 30, Folder 5)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews - 78, 82, 90, 93, & 94
      - Soviet Jews, no. 6, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 30, Folder 6)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews - 106, 107, 109, & 112
      - Soviet Jews, no. 7, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 30, Folder 7)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews - 115, 116, 117, 119, & 120
      - Soviet Jews, no. 8, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 30, Folder 8)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews - 121, 122, 123, & 125
      - Soviet Jews, no. 9, photographs: b&w; 41 x 51 cm. (Box 30, Folder 9)
        Images from contact sheets Soviet Jews - 133, 136, 137, 140, 143, 153, 155, & 157
    - Project files
      - Soviet Jews: [correspondence, clippings, & notes] (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Soviet Jews: [exhibit captions] (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Soviet Jews: Emigre family reunion (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Roman Vishniak Project, Series 3
  This single-folder series contains contact sheets of photographs that Ira Nowinski took of Roman Vishniak's art studio upon Vishniak's death.
  - Vishniak, Roman: contact sheets 1 - 2 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Negatives, Series 4
  This series contains the negatives of the various Jewish-related images in this collection.
  - Holocaust: Austria: Mauthausen, sheets 1 - 51987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Holocaust: Germany: Berlin, sheets 1-61987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Holocaust: Germany: Sachseuhausen, sheets 7-121987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Holocaust: Buchenwald, sheets 13-221987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Holocaust: Germany: Ravensbruck, Dachau, sheets 23-321987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Holocaust: Germany: Neungamme, Berges-Belsem, sheets 33-411987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Holocaust: Paris, Amsterdam, sheets 1-2, 11987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Holocaust: Philly IFM, Judah Magues IFM, N. U. C. IFM, sheet 11987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Holocaust: Israel: Yad Vashem, Yad Mordechi, Tel Aviv, Jerusalem, Freedom Fighter Kibbutz, sheets 1-151987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Holocaust: unmarked, sheets 1-151987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 2.25 in. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Holocaust: unmarked, sheets 16-311987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 2.25 in. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Holocaust: unmarked, unidentified contact sheet1987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 2.25 in. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Holocaust: Poland: Warsaw, sheets 1 - 81987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Holocaust: Poland: Auschwitz, sheets 9 - 161987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Holocaust: Poland: Birkenau, sheets 17 - 261987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Holocaust: Poland: Treblinka, sheets 27 - 301987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Holocaust: Poland: Maidanek, sheets 31 - 371987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Holocaust: Poland, sheets 38 - 451987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Sobibor (sheets 38 - 39) -- Belzcu (sheet 40) -- Lodz (sheet 41 - 42) -- Krakow (sheet 43) -- Lublin (sheet 44-45)
  - Holocaust: Poland: 50th Anniversary of the Warsaw Ghetto Uprising, sheets 46 - 561987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Holocaust: Poland: 50th Anniversary of the Warsaw Ghetto Uprising, sheets 57 - 701987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Holocaust: Poland: 50th Anniversary of the Warsaw Ghetto Uprising, sheets 71 - 841987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Holocaust: Poland: Krakow, sheets 85 - 911987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Holocaust: Poland: Birkenau & Auschwitz, sheets 92 - 1031987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Holocaust: Poland: Plaszow, Lublin-Lodz, Maidanek, sheets 104 - 1131987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Holocaust: Poland: Treblinka, Sobibor, Belcz, sheets 114 - 1221987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Holocaust: Segal Memorial, sheets 1 - 151987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 26)
    San Francisco & New Jersey
  - Holocaust: Segal Memorial, sheets 16 - 281987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Holocaust: Segal Memorial, sheets 29 - 341987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 2.25 in. (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Holocaust: Washington, D.C., sheets 1 - 111987 - 1995, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Karaite, California, sheets 1 - 171985, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Karaite '85: Egypt, sheets 1 - 131985, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Karaite '85: Israel, sheets 14 - 301985, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Karaite '85: Israel, sheets 31 - 511985, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Karaite: Israel, sheets 1 - 111989, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jews of San Francisco, sheets 1 - 15, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jews of San Francisco, sheets 16 - 30, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jews of San Francisco, sheets 31 - 45, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jews of San Francisco, sheets 46 - 60, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jews of San Francisco, sheets 61 - 75, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jews of San Francisco, sheets 76 - 90, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jews of San Francisco, sheets 91 - 105, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jews of San Francisco, sheets 106 - 120, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jews of San Francisco, sheets 121 - 135, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jews of San Francisco, sheets 136 - 150, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jews of San Francisco, sheets 151 - 165, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jews of San Francisco, sheets 166 - 180, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Vishniak, Roman, negatives: b&w; 35 mm. (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Cafe Society project, 1977-1981, Series 5; 33 photographic prints
  This series contains photographic prints of images that were included in Ira Nowinksi's photographic essay The Cafe Society
  - Cafe Society: prints, 1977-1981, Accession no. 2003-256; 33 photographs: b&w; 37 x 28 cm. (Box 31)
    Purchased from Ira Nowinski